213-926-0655

MikeyLashaun@icloud.com 7425 Sepulveda Blvd. Van Nuys, Ca 91405

Profile

Very strong organizational skills, ability to pick up new processes and procedures quickly, extremely social, highly motivated, team worker, and dedicated to completing the task at hand. I have worked a multitude of jobs, all in which requires me to have excellent customer service personality.

Skills

- Resourceful problem solver
- Fast Pace worker
- Quick Learner
- Efficient in Microsoft Programs:
 - Word
 - Power Point
 - Excel
- Organizational Skills:
 - Scheduling
 - Time Management
 - Assertive
 - Hands On worker

Experience

BARTENDER, BENIHANA'S, SANTA MONICA, CA JUNE 2016- PRESENT

- Able to craft a variety of cocktails, shooters, and mixed drinks.
- Do to the nature of the position I am excellent at serving lunch and dinner courses. Also, bussing my bar and tables surrounding it.
- Restocking and prepping for future incoming customers.
- Taking and recording inventory.
- Able to pour and serve draft beers correctly.

DISK JOCKEY (DJ) LIVE ENGINEER, YNOT ENERTAINMENT, LOS ANGELES, CA - MAY 2008-PRESENT

• Lapprenticed with two DJ's.



213-926-0655 MikeyLashaun@icloud.com 7425 Sepulveda Blvd. Van Nuys, Ca 91405

- Calculating the demographics of a facility to set up DJ equipment, i.e., speakers, bass cabinets, lights, mixer, turntables, to achieve the best auditory harmonics.
- Master of Ceremonies; catering ceremonies to fit the demographic of the crowd.
- Playing music to fit the setting in mood of the occasion.
- Inventory control of equipment.
- Purchasing goods and equipment.

FOOD CARRIER, GRUBHUB, SANTA MONICA, CA – FEBRUARY 2015- APRIL 2016
DECISION MAKING IN ORDER TO ASSURE PROPER TIME MANAGEMENT FOR THE TIMELY PICKING UP AND DE-LIVERY OF FOOD.

- Regular and ongoing communication between employer and customers.
- Solving delivery problems due to restaurant delays, traffic, etc.
- Building professional and collaborative relationships with the restaurants and customers as representing the face of GrubHub and myself.

DRIVER, LYFT, SANTA MONICA, CA-MAY 2014- FEBRUARY 2015

- Built versatile customer interactions to establish inviting atmospheres.
- Set my own schedule/timetable.
- Chose work locations based on demand.
- Helped customers with packages/luggage.

ASSISTANT A&R, SONY RECORDS, BURBANK, CA - JUNE 2013- MAY 2014

- Internship which involved:.
 - Screened issues before they met the manager. Planned and reviewed the schedule for each day.
 - Constant note taking and reminder settings in a very interactive environment.
 - Personal driver to all events of the day.
 - Created charts and background information regarding our artist in scope.
 - Drafted and responded to artist, producers, and other crucial cliental.
 - Filtered instrumentals and lyrics before reaching further in the process.

CREW MEMBER, MCDONALDS, LOS ANGELES, CA - JUNE 2011-DECEMBER 2012

• Frequently rotated in the following work stations/job duties:

213-926-0655 MikeyLashaun@icloud.com 7425 Sepulveda Blvd. Van Nuys, Ca 91405

- Front counter,
- Drive through window,
- Kitchen worker/cook.
- Helped drive sales goals and achieve monthly standard for the mystery shopper.
- Resolved customer complaints and conflicts.
- Restocking and documenting all product.
- I worked on a very flexible schedule and was able to take all shifts from opening, closing, weekend, and holidays.

Education

Santa Monica College, Santa Monica, California – Associates in Computer ScienceMay, 2010 to Present